const STORE= [
    {
        question: '1. Which wine usually pairs best with seafood?',
        answers: [
            "A. Red wine", 
            "B. Sparkling wine",
            "C. White wines",
            "D. B & C"
          ],
        correctAnswer: "D. B & C"
    },
    {
        question: "2. What temperature should champagne typically be served at (Fahrenheit)?",
        answers: [
            60,
            45,
            35,
            65],
        correctAnswer: 45
    },
    { 
        question: "3. Where does tannin come from?",
        answers: [
            "A. Grape Skins",
            "B. Wooden Barrels",
            "C. Grape seeds & stems",
            "D. All of the above"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "D. All of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "4. California winemaking first became popular with which type of wine?",
        answers: [
            "A. Zinfindel",
            "B. Rosé",
            "C. Malbec",
            "D. Pinot Grigio"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A. Zinfindel"
    },
    {
        question: "5. Champagne can be made in:",
        answers: [
            "A. Only Champagne, FR",
            "B. Across Europe",
            "C. Anywhere Pinot Nior vines grow",
            "D. In France and Italy only"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A. Only Champagne, FR"
    },

    { question: "6. Napa Valley is best known for the following wines:",
    answers: [
        "A. Chardonnay & Cabernet Sauvignon",
        "B. Sparkling wine & Zinfindel",
        "C. Malbec & Chardonnay",
        "D. None, Napa is not a good climate for wine"
    ],
        correctAnswer: "A. Chardonnay & Cabernet Sauvignon"
    },
    {
        question: "7. Noble rot is: ",
        answers: [
            "A. What happens when wine turns bad",
            "B. Sometimes happens to unpicked overripe grapes",
            "C. Can happen in the wine making process, if they don’t put enough sugar in the wine",
            "D. Is the name of a popular California winery"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B. Sometimes happens to unpicked overripe grapes"

    },
    {
        question: "8. Chardonnay is made with ______ barrels: ",
        answers: [
            "A. Stainless steel",
            "B. Plastic",
            "C. Oak",
            "D. Any, it depends on the wine maker’s preference "
        ],
        correctAnswer: "D. Any, it depends on the wine maker’s preference "

    },
    {
        question: "9.  Unopened wine should typically be stored:",
        answers: [
            "A. On its side",
            "B. Upright",
            "C. It does not matter, as log as it is in a cool/dark place ",
            "D. It depends on the type of wine"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A. On its side"

    },
    {
        question: "10. Sauternes is an example of: ",
        answers: [
            "A. Fortified wine",
            "B. A popular California winery ",
            "C. Sweet wine",
            "D. Full-bodied red wine" 
        ],
        correctAnswer: "C. Sweet wine"

    }

]